Hi, it's me Ulrich.
大家好 我是Ulrich.
Well you know. Of course I'm late .
你了解我的 我又迟到了
Um, as usual. Not always a great student. Not always on time.
就像以往一样 不是个好学生 经常迟到
So this is no exception.
这次我也不例外
Here I am to wish everybody a happy anniversary,
祝愿大家周年快乐
Hope we can all get together and celebrate.
希望我们能团聚在一起庆祝
Um of course we'll all be thinking about our favorite frenemy Sissi
当然了 我们都会想起我们最喜欢的亦敌亦友Sissi
and sending lots of love up to heaven to Jodi who we miss very much.
同时缅怀已经逝去的Jodi
And also,
与此同时
well you know I don't know what to say I'm kind of shy I'm not a guy for words.
你知道我有点害羞腼腆不善言辞
So thanks for being out there for all of us all these years,
那么感谢大家这么多年来的陪伴
and happy 15th anniversary guys.
再次祝福大家15周年快乐
Take care.
祝好
Hope we can all get together again soon.
希望我们很快还能再见
Bye bye.
拜拜
You all warriors, it's William.
所有Lyoko勇士们你们好 我是William
I just wanted to say thanks for all your loyalty over the years.
我想先感谢大家这些年来对Code Lyoko的忠心耿耿
Speaking of loyalty, a special thank you to all those people who believed me
说到忠心耿耿 特别感谢那些人
when I said I never wanted to break up Yumi and Ulrich.
相信我决不会断绝和Yumi还有Ulrich的关系
注：特别注意这里原文用的like，用斜体表示强调
I just like Yumi, doesn't everybody?
我只是喜欢 Yumi 不是吗
Anyway, a special shout-out to Jodi who we all love.
不管怎样 特别要缅怀我们喜爱的Jodi
And you guys remember, if you stick together, no evil can defeat you.
要记得 如果大家都拧成一股绳 就无人能敌
Hi, this is Odd from Code Lyoko.
大家好 这儿是Code Lyoko的Odd
I want to thank all our fans on this 15 year anniversary celebration.
我想感谢所有参与15周年纪念活动的粉丝
All your love and appreciation makes me so crazy happy.
你们给我带来的爱与欣赏让我激动不已
I just wanna,
我现在只想尬歌一曲
Break! Break! Break dance!
霹雳 霹雳 霹雳舞
Break! Break! Break dance! Here we goooo-oooo-oo!
霹雳 霹雳 我们一起来跳霹雳舞
And I would also like to shout out to heaven to our dear and very beloved friend and colleague Jodi Forrest
同样我也特别缅怀我们逝去的受人喜爱的朋友和同事Jodi Forrest
who voiced my frenemy Sissi and my favorite science teacher in the world, Mrs. Hertz.
Jodi Forrest给我的亦敌亦友Sissi还有我最喜欢的科学老师Hertz女士配了音
Happy Code Lyoko 15-year anniversary.
Code Lyoko 15周年愉快
Love to all.
爱大家(￣3￣)
Hi it's Jeremy.
大家好 这里是Jeremy
And Aelita.
还有Aelita
We really appreciate everyone remembering that it's our 15th anniversary.
我诚挚地感谢所有记得Code Lyoko 15周年纪念日的粉丝
Wow time sure flies.
哇 时间过得真快
It's hard to believe we're already 15.
难以置信 Code Lyoko已经15岁了
Yeah, I mean I still fit in all my turtleneck sweaters.
没错 我是说我还能穿进我之前穿过的高领毛衣
[Laughter]
哈哈哈
Before we go, we'd like you to join us in sending a burst of heavenly love to our dear friend Jodi Forrest.
结束之前 我们希望你能和我们一起深深地祝愿我们逝去的亲爱的朋友Jodi Forrest
We love you Jodi.
我们爱你 Jodi
Yeah we love you Jodi.
没错 我们爱你 Jodi
All the best to all our fans.
大家万事如意
Virtualisation.
虚拟化
All the best to all our fans.
大家万事如意
Virtualisation.
虚拟化
注：有待进一步考证
I don't think I've ever said that before.
我不记得我之前有说过这句话诶
Yeah, no matter.
没事啦
Hey there, Lyoko warriors.
Lyoko勇士们你们好
This is your old friend Jim.
这是你们的老朋友Jim
注：这句话没听清……
Jimbo, the Gymboree no.
Listen, I want to thank you for all your loyalty over the years.
听着 我想感谢你们这些年来对Code Lyoko的忠心耿耿
You really kept the faith.
你们确实保有着信念
However I have noticed that some of you are not in top physical condition.
不过呢我发现你们有些人身体有点不够好啊
So I'd like you all right now wherever you are to get down and give me 20 good ones.
所以我现在希望你们现在马上趴下给我来20个标准俯卧撑
10... no... nobody? Em, forget it.
那做十个怎么样……没人吗 算了
Speaking of loyalty, I just want to send a special message to Jodi.
说到忠心耿耿 我想对Jodi说几句话
We loved her.
我们喜欢她
She was the best of us.
她是我们中最棒的
If there's a place where good people go white,
如果有天堂存在
that's where she is.
那她肯定去那儿了
Thanks a lot guys.
非常感谢大家
Know this: The future holds something special and exciting for each of us.
记住这个 未来对每个人都是特殊且激动人心的
but I... I can't talk about it.
但我……我说不下去了
压制，时间轴，翻译：布尔
片源(03:45-04:03)：NAVras_Z，Odd_HD
Code Lyoko 15周年快乐
企划协助者
编剧
缅怀